Lowell Thomas Papers: Periodicals
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. National Geographic, 1910-1981; 8 boxes
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXII Number Five, November 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXII Number Six, December 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIII Number One, January 1958 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIII Number Two, February 1958 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIII Number Three, March 1958 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIII Number Four, April 1958 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIII Number Five, May 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIII Number Six, June 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIV Number One, July 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIV Number Two, August 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIV Number Two, August 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIV Number Three, September 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIV Number Four, October 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIV Number Five, November 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXIV Number Six, December 1958 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXV Number One, January 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXV Number Two, February 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXV, NO. 3, March 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXV, NO. 4, April 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXV, NO. 5, May 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXV, NO. 6, June 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXVI, NO. 1, July 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXVI, NO. 2, August 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXVI, NO. 3, September 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXVI, NO. 3, September 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXVI, NO. 4, October 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXVI, NO. 5, November 1959 (Box 6)
  - The National Geographic Magazine VOL. CXVI, NO. 5, November 1959 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. CXVI, NO. 6, December 1959 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 118, NO. 1, July 1960 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 118, NO. 3, September 1960 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 118, NO. 4, October 1960 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 118, NO. 5, November 1960 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 118, NO. 5, November 1960 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 118, NO. 6, December 1960 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 123, NO. 2, February 1963 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 124, NO. 4, October 1963 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 125, NO. 2, February 1964 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 125, NO. 3, March 1964 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 125, NO. 3, March 1964 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 125, NO. 3, March 1964 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 126, NO. 5, November 1964 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 127, NO. 1, January 1965 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 131, NO. 1, January 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 131, NO. 2, February 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 131, NO. 3, March 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 131, NO. 4, April 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 131, NO. 5, May 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 131, NO. 6, June 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 132, NO. 1, July 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 132, NO. 2, August 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 132, NO. 3, September 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 132, NO. 4, October 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 132, NO. 5, November 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 132, NO. 6, December 1967 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 133, NO. 1, January 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 133, NO. 2, February 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 133, NO. 3, March 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 133, NO. 4, April 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 133, NO. 5, May 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 133, NO. 6, June 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 134, NO. 1, July 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 134, NO. 2, August 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic VOL. 134, NO. 3, September 1968 (Box 6)
  - National Geographic [VOL. 134, NO. 4], October 1968 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 134, NO. 5, November 1968 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 134, NO. 6, December 1968 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 135, NO. 1, January 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 135, NO. 2, February 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 135, NO. 3, March 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 135, NO. 4, April 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 135, NO. 6, June 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 136, NO. 1, July 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 136, NO. 2, August 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 136, NO. 4, October 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 136, NO. 5, November 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 136, NO. 6, December 1969 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 137, NO. 1, January 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 137, NO. 2, February 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 137, NO. 3, March 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 137, NO. 4, April 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 137, NO. 5, May 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 138, NO. 1, July 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 138, NO. 2, August 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 138, NO. 3, September 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 138, NO. 4, October 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 138, NO. 5, November 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 138, NO. 6, December 1970 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic [VOL. 139, NO. 1], January 1971 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 139, NO. 2, February 1971 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 139, NO. 3, March 1971 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 139, NO. 4, April 1971 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 139, NO. 6, June 1971 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 140, NO. 2, August 1971 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 140, NO. 3, September 1971 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 141, NO. 1, January 1972 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 142, NO. 2, August 1972 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 142, NO. 2, August 1972 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 142, NO. 3, September 1972 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 142, NO. 4, October 1972 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 142, NO. 5, November 1972 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 142, NO. 6, December 1972 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 143, NO. 1, January 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 143, NO. 1, January 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 143, NO. 2, February 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 143, NO. 3, March 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 143, NO. 4, April 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 143, NO. 5, May 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 143, NO. 6, June 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 144, NO. 1, July 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 144, NO. 1, July 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 144, NO. 2, August 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 144, NO. 3, September 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 144, NO. 4, October 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 144, NO. 5, November 1973 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 145, NO. 1, January 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 145, NO. 2, February 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 145, NO. 3, March 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 145, NO. 4, April 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 145, NO. 5, May 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 145, NO. 6, June 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 146, NO. 1, July 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 146, NO. 2, August 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 146, NO. 3, September 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 146, NO. 3, September 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 146, NO. 4, October 1974 (Box 7)
  - National Geographic VOL. 146, NO. 5, November 1974 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 146, NO. 6, December 1974 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 147, NO. 1, January 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 147, NO. 2, February 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 147, NO. 3, March 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 147, NO. 4, April 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 147, NO. 5, May 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 147, NO. 6, June 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 148, NO. 1, July 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 148, NO. 2, August 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 148, NO. 3, September 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 148, NO. 4, October 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 148, NO. 5, November 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 148, NO. 6, December 1975 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 149, NO. 1, January 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 149, NO. 2, February 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 149, NO. 3, March 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 149, NO. 4, April 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 149, NO. 5, May 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 149, NO. 6, June 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 149, NO. 6, June 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 150, NO. 1, July 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 150, NO. 2, August 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 150, NO. 3, September 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 150, NO. 4, October 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 150, NO. 5, November 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 150, NO. 6, December 1976 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 151, NO. 1, January 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 151, NO. 2, February 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 151, NO. 3, March 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 151, NO. 4, April 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 151, NO. 6, June 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 152, NO. 1, July 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 152, NO. 2, August 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 152, NO. 4, October 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 152, NO. 5, November 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 152, NO. 6, December 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 153, NO. 2, February 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 153, NO. 4, April 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 153, NO. 5, May 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 153, NO. 6, June 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 154, NO. 1, July 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 154, NO. 2, August 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 154, NO. 3, September 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 154, NO. 4, October 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 154, NO. 5, November 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 154, NO. 6, December 1978 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 155, NO. 1, January 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 155, NO. 2, February 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 155, NO. 3, March 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 155, NO. 4, April 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 155, NO. 5, May 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 155, NO. 6, June 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 156, NO. 1, July 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 156, NO. 2, August 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 156, NO. 3, September 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 156, NO. 4, October 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 156, NO. 5, November 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 156, NO. 6, December 1979 (Box 8)
  - National Geographic VOL. 160, NO. 3, September 1981 (Box 8)
- 2. Geographical Review, 1926-1978; 3 boxes
  Series contains issues of Geographical Review.
  - Geographical Review VOL. XVI. NO. 4, October 1926 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XVII, NO. 1, January 1927 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XVII, NO. 2, April 1927 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XVII, NO. 3, July 1927 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XVIII, NO. 1, January 1928 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XVIII, NO. 2, April 1928 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XVIII, NO. 3, July 1928 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XIX, NO. 1, January 1929 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XIX, NO. 2, April 1929 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XIX, NO. 3, July 1929 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XIX, NO. 4, October 1929 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XX, NO. 1, January 1930 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XX, NO. 2, April 1930 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XX, NO. 3, July 1930 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXI, NO. 3, July 1931 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXI, NO. 4, October 1931 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXII, NO. 1, January 1932 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXIII, NO. 3, July 1933 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXIV, NO. 1, January 1934 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXIV, NO. 3, July 1934 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXIV, NO. 4, October 1934 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXV, NO. 1, January 1935 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXV, NO. 2, April 1935 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXV, NO. 3, July 1935 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXV, NO. 4, October 1935 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVI, NO. 1, January 1936 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVI, NO. 2, April 1936 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVI, NO. 4, October 1936 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVII, NO. 1, January 1937 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVII, NO. 2, April 1937 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVII, NO. 3, July 1937 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVII, NO. 4, October 1937 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVIII, NO. 1, January 1938 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVIII, NO. 2, April 1938 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXVIII, NO. 4, October 1938 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXIX, NO. 1, January 1939 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXIX, NO. 4, October 1939 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXI, NO. 3, July 1941 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXII, NO. 3, July 1942 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXII, NO. 4, October 1942 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIII, NO. 1, January 1943 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIII, NO. 2, April 1943 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIII, NO. 3, July 1943 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIII, NO. 4, October 1943 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIV, NO. 1, January 1944 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIV, NO. 2, April 1944 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIV, NO. 3, July 1944 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIV, NO. 4, October 1944 (Box 9)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXV, NO. 1, January 1945 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXV, NO. 2, April 1945 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXV, NO. 3, July 1945 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXV, NO. 4, October 1945 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVI, NO. 1, January 1946 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVI, NO. 2, April 1946 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVI, NO. 3, July 1946 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVI, NO. 4, October 1946 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVII, NO. 1, January 1947 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVII, NO. 2, April 1947 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVII, NO. 3, July 1947 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVII, NO. 4, October 1947 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVIII, NO. 1, January 1948 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVIII, NO. 2, April 1948 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXVIII, NO. 4, October 1948 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIX, NO. 1, January 1949 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIX, NO. 3, July 1949 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XXXIX, NO. 4, October 1949 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XL, NO. 1, January 1950 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XL, NO. 3, July 1950 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XL, NO. 4, October 1950 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLI, NO. 2, April 1951 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLI, NO. 3, July 1951 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLII, NO. 1, January 1952 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLII, NO. 2, April 1952 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLII, NO. 4, October 1952 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIII, NO. 1, January 1953 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIII, NO. 2, April 1953 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIII, NO. 3, July 1953 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIV, NO. 2, April 1954 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIV, NO. 2, April 1954 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIV, NO. 3, July 1954 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIV, NO. 4, October 1954 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLV, NO. 1, January 1955 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLV, NO. 2, April 1955 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLV, NO. 3, July 1955 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLV, NO. 4, October 1955 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVI, NO. 1, January 1956 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVI, NO. 2, April 1956 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVI, NO. 3, July 1956 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVI, NO. 4, October 1956 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVII, NO. 1, January 1957 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVII, NO. 2, April 1957 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVII, NO. 3, July 1957 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVII, NO. 4, October 1957 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVIII, NO. 1, January 1958 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVIII, NO. 2, April 1958 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVIII, NO. 3, July 1958 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLVIII, NO. 4, October 1958 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIX, NO. 1, January 1959 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIX, NO. 2, April 1959 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIX, NO. 3, July 1959 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. XLIX, NO. 4, October 1959 (Box 10)
  - Geographical Review VOL. L, NO. 1, January 1960 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. L, NO. 2, April 1960 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. L, NO. 3, July 1960 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. L, NO. 4, October 1960 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LI, NO. 1, January 1961 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LI, NO. 3, July 1961 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LII, NO. 1, January 1962 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LII, NO. 2, April 1962 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LII, NO. 3, July 1962 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LII, NO. 4, October 1962 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIII, NO. 1, January 1963 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIII, NO. 2, April 1963 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIII, NO. 4, October 1963 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIV, NO. 1, January 1964 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIV, NO. 2, April 1964 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIV, NO. 3, July 1964 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LV, NO. 3, July 1965 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LV, NO. 4, October 1965 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVI, NO. 1, January 1966 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVI, NO. 3, July 1966 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVI, NO. 4, October 1966 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVII, NO. 1, January 1967 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVII, NO. 1, January 1967 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVII, NO. 2, April 1967 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVII, NO. 3, July 1967 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVII, NO. 4, October 1967 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVIII, NO. 1, January 1968 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVIII, NO. 2, April 1968 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVIII, NO. 3, July 1968 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LVIII, NO. 4, October 1968 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIX, NO. 1, January 1969 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIX, NO. 2, April 1969 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIX, NO. 3, July 1969 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LIX, NO. 4, October 1969 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LX, NO. 1, January 1970 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LX, NO. 3, July 1970 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LX, NO. 4, October 1970 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXI, NO. 1, January 1971 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXII, NO. 3, July 1972 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXII, NO. 4, October 1972 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXIII, NO. 3, July 1973 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXIII, NO. 4, October 1973 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXIV, NO. 1, January 1974 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXIV, NO. 2, April 1974 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXIV, NO. 3, July 1974 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXIV, NO. 4, October 1974 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXV, NO. 1, January 1975 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. LXV, NO. 2, April 1975 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 65, NO. 3, July 1975 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 65, NO. 4, October 1975 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 66, NO. 1, January 1976 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 66, NO. 3, July 1976 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 66, NO. 4, October 1976 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 67, NO. 1, January 1977 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 67, NO. 2, April 1977 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 67, NO. 3, July 1977 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 67, NO. 4, October 1977 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 68, NO. 1, January 1978 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 68, NO. 2, April 1978 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 68, NO. 3, July 1978 (Box 11)
  - Geographical Review VOL. 68, NO. 4, October 1978 (Box 11)
- 3. The Geographical Journal, 1924-1982; 4 boxes
  Series contains numerous issues of The Geographical Journal.
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXIV No. 2, August 1924 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXV No. 5, May 1925 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXV No. 6, June 1925 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVI No. 1, July 1925 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVI No. 2, August 1925 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVI No. 3, September 1925 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVI No. 4, October 1925 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVI No. 5, November 1925 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVI No. 6, December 1925 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVII No. 1, January 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVII No. 2, February 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVII No. 3, March 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVII No. 5, May 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVII No. 6, June 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVIII No. 1, July 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVIII No. 2, August 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVIII No. 3, September 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVIII No. 4, October 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVIII No. 5, November 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXVIII No. 6, December 1926 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXIX No. 1, January 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXIX No. 2, February 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXIX No. 3, March 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXIX No. 4, April 1927 (Box 12)